MADHAVI NAYAK

(UI / UX Designer & Developer)

Contact No.: +91-8507881458

E-Mail ID: madhavi.nayak16@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To excel in my field through hard work, skills and perseverance and obtain a challenging position in organization that gives me an opportunity for acquiring new skills and knowledge to pursue a successful career.

EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

Having **3 years** of experience as a **UI / UX Designer & Developer**. Having good experience in Web Designing through technologies like HTML5, CSS3, Angular2, AngularJS, JavaScript, JQuery, NodeJS, Bootstrap, Photoshop, WordPress, etc.

- ➤ I can adapt to professional environment and effectively communicate with Team Members and various stakeholders.
- ➤ I am hardworking and very sincere in my work.
- ➤ I am dedicated, determined and diligent by nature.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Company	Cosmo Solutions Pvt. Ltd., Gurgaon
Designation	UI / UX Designer & Developer
Duration	September 2020 – Till Date
Skills	HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Photoshop, WordPress
Projects	Ultrashop, Naturish, Skylark, Cartmarket
	https://www.themeatlas.com/
	https://www.themeatlas.com/item/121/ultrashop
	http://139.59.62.233/development/jalaj/ultrashop-v2/
	http://139.59.62.233/development/jalaj/Naturish_Ver_3/
Responsibilities	➤ Setup the WordPress Themes
	➤ Install Plugins for Themes
	➤ GAP analysis, identification and fixing bugs in Theme
	Create Logos and Banners in Photoshop as per the requirement
	Creating PSD Templates in Photoshop
	Working on Documentation

Company	9TAB Digitech Pvt. Ltd., Noida
Designation	UI / UX Developer & Designer
Duration	January 2020 – March 2020
Skills	HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Photoshop
Project	IndiaeCash (URL: https://indiaecash.co.in/#/login?returnUrl=%2F)
	This project is development of a Website for Baking Sector. Working
	on HTML page, JavaScript and Photoshop to design UI/UX for below
	services in the website;
	➤ Login & Registration Page
	Project Logo using Photoshop
	Designing background images using Photoshop
	Designed Webpages for below services;
	 Mobile Recharge
	 Bill Payments
	Ticket Booking (Air, Train and Bus)
	 AEPS (Aadhaar Enabled Payment System)
	 PAN Card Form
	Insurance
	Cash Withdraw

Company	MobiMonster, Gurgaon
Designation	UI / UX Developer
Duration	June 2019 – December 2019
Skills	HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap
Project	2G/3G Project
	This project is development of a software to track and prevent hacking
	software from hacking phone calls. Working on HTML page and
	JavaScript to design UI/UX for this software.
Project	Android Project
	Working on basic ASP.NET and on SQL for database.

Company	Lakshyaleaders Education Software Pvt. Ltd., Bangalore
Designation	Assistant System Engineer
Duration	August 2016 – November 2017
Skills	HTML5, CSS3, Angular2, AngularJS, JavaScript, JQuery, NodeJS,
	Photoshop, XAML
Project	Lakshyalife Project (URL: https://lakshyalife.in/)
	Working on HTML page in whole project and also design first page.
Project	AngularCli Project
	Create kendo angular grid and binding data in grid.
Project	Bootstrap Angular4 Project
	Working on HTML page in whole project.

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

B.Sc. (Information Technology) [2015]

Kuvempu University, Bangalore

CERTIFICATE COURSES

- ➤ Higher Diploma in Information Technology from NIIT
- Diploma in Infoedge

INTERESTS

I like Cooking, Painting, Watching TV, Travelling & Shopping.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name Mr. Ranjit Prasad Nayak

Gender Female **Marital Status** Married

Correspondence Flat No. 402, Building No. 631, Lane No. 4, Westend Marg,

Address Saidulajab, Saket, New Delhi – 110030

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

(MADHAVI NAYAK)